Oh! What the…
Is that, uh…
Rune.
Hey, Rune.
- It's morning.
- Mmm?
- Sleep okay?
- Hmm?
- How did you sleep?
- Pretty good.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Look, it's so sunny outside.
Whoa, yeah, perfect weather.
Hyah!
Hey, come on. Knock it off.
Hands to yourself.
- Let's get ready.
- On it.
- We should wash up, gotta put on my face.
- Mmm.
I'm gonna return
the clothes and the watch.
- Hmm?
- The clothes and the watch.
MIMI (29)
HOSTESS
I'll do it myself.
- You'll return them?
- Yeah.
- I wanna talk to them anyway.
- Okay.
RUNE (28)
RAPPER/BUSINESS OWNER
- I gotcha.
- Yeah.
- I'll leave it to you, then.
- Okay.
- Just don't start a fight, okay?
- I won't.
- I'm gonna hold you to it.
- I swear.
In terms of our emotional distance,
I don't know,
I definitely think we got closer.
Like, I don't feel nervous around him.
Man, I had so much fun.
Waking up together was the best.
A lot of guys
are trying to hit on Mimi here…
but they don't stand a chance.
I'm 1,000% sure now.
Our goddess is finally
coming back today, Maru.
Hell yeah.
You don't have anything to say?
About what Rune said when they left
yesterday? Come on, don't lie.
He was like, "You guys lost."
We may have lost the battle,
but the war ain't over yet.
Hmm.
Maybe I should bring it up
while we're eating.
It's a beautiful day.
I don't know,
do you think it'll get messy if I do?
I mean, not that I give a crap.
LOUNGE
- Hands together.
- All right.
Thank you for this amazing feast.
Let's eat!
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
Dig in, y'all!
- Could pass that bowl?
- I'm starving.
- We're back.
- Morning, here we are.
- Welcome.
- We started eating.
You guys look tired.
What's with the smiles?
- Where are my clothes?
- Have a seat.
- Well…
- Any room here?
- Should I move over?
- She can go there.
- Kamaken, can you move down?
- Sure.
Thank you.
- So tell us.
- Huh?
- We just had breakfast.
- Yeah.
- Can you scoot over?
- That does look cramped.
- Man, you took a ton of photos. Wow!
- Ooh, let's see.
Yeah, we did a full room tour.
- Took photos of everything.
- Can I see? Oh, wow.
- You had two beds? Not just one?
- Sounds nice.
- A villa with a pool? Wow, that's awesome.
- It's so gorgeous!
- Knew it'd be dope.
- Nice, right?
- Here's your plate, Rune.
- It was awesome. Thank you.
Wow, it's actually super fancy too.
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
- Right?
- It was incredible.
- The villa is crazy nice.
- And it comes with a pool.
- Go for a swim?
- What was the best part?
Hmm, that's a tough one.
- We were drinking until 3 in the morning.
- What'd you guys do?
- You were drinking that long?
- Dang.
- Then what?
- We ran out of alcohol.
- You kept drinking until it was all gone?
- Mmm.
- That's crazy.
- Wait, did you guys get massages too?
- Did it go by fast?
- Man, that sounds nice.
Yeah, it flew by.
- Sounds like fun.
- Totally.
- What are you doing?
- All right, it's time.
- Tai-chan?
- Come with me.
- Where?
- Outside.
What?
- You wanna do this now?
- Yeah.
With everyone here?
That's why we should go out the damn room.
- Who the hell you think you're talking to?
- Come on, hurry up.
Maru, get over here.
You're part of this too. Let's go.
- Wait, why?
- Why him?
Maru didn't even say anything though.
- What?
- Get your ass outside.
If you wanna talk,
then drop the damn attitude, bro.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
KITASHINCHI'S NO.1 HOSTESS
BLEEDING BIG-SIS ENERGY
MIMI
STRAIGHT-SHOOTING FORMER MMA CHAMP
KAMAKEN
POPULAR OKINAWAN HOSTESS LOOKING FOR LOVE
KAHOCHI
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
- Yesterday, we were at the gates.
- Yeah.
And right before you left,
you were like, "So that's how it is."
But then you walked away
before you said what you meant.
If you got something to say,
say it to our faces.
don't write it in a letter. It's pathetic.
- Same with you.
- What?
- You handed her your watch.
- You got a problem with that?
You lost fair and square,
so back off and stay in your room.
Going behind my back like that.
Both you guys lost to me, right?
- And then you came sneaking around again.
- We weren't sneaking around.
- Oh, yeah?
- It's not over. I'm just getting started.
- It's over for you.
- I lost that battle. Who cares?
- What?
- Back off.
- Whoa, whoa.
- What the hell?
Take a swing. Try something.
- You first.
- Hit me, you little bitch.
Go on. Hit me, motherfucker! Come here!
- Come on, you little shit.
- You still tough? Come on!
- Watch it!
- I'll kill you!
Guys!
Okay, stop. That's enough.
Break it up. Let go.
Come on, let go. Get off him.
All right, easy.
You want some too? Come at me.
What? You that pissed
we gave her some stuff?
Like I give a shit
about punk-ass losers like you.
Don't test me, bro.
- Try me.
- Huh?
Look at you,
shaking and trying to act tough.
You little…
Hey!
What did you just say to me?
Let's go. Come here.
- Chill out, dumbass.
- Oh, now you're too scared?
- Say what?
- Come at me!
Relax.
- Hmm?
- Let's go to the classroom and talk.
- Maru. Maru.
- Walk it off, okay?
Maru.
Let's go to the classroom. Let's talk.
You spent all this time
going on about Ayacheru.
- What? No, are--
- Then you give Mimi your watch,
saying crap like,
"I want to lose track of time."
Like I said, it's none
of your goddamn business! Got it?
We did this fair and square, right?
- You should've waited.
- I get what you're saying.
I shouldn't have to hold back.
I'm gonna do what I want.
- Okay. I'm good to talk like this.
- I know. Listen--
There was a girl
who was excited to go on a date.
Uh-huh.
Then you gave her something
and said you trusted her,
that she should wait for you.
To put all that on her is asking a lot.
That's something I can ask her myself.
- Fine.
- Why can't we leave it at that?
You should've waited till she came back
to say all that.
I get that.
- But I have to be true to what I feel.
- We all do.
I don't wanna hold back to be nice
and end up not putting myself out there.
You know?
We're both gonna do our best,
see what happens. Fair and square.
- That's it, right?
- Yeah, I guess so. Cool.
- I'm good with that.
- Leave it at that.
We good?
Okay, we're done here.
Tai-chan, you ready?
Yeah. But I want to talk to him alone.
Okay.
- Remember what you said about mealtimes?
- Mealtimes?
Yeah, when we eat,
you said something like,
it's supposed to be a fun, friendly space
for everyone, with no drama.
That's how it should be, but I ruined that
today, and I feel bad about that.
It's just that, no matter what happened,
I felt I had to see her off at the gate.
- That felt like the right move.
- I understand where you're coming from.
The clothes and letter were ready.
It's obvious
you thought about it beforehand.
Yeah, but I get how you felt too,
seeing us do that right in front of you.
I should've thought about that,
but I couldn't 'cause, like…
It felt like that was all I could do
in the moment. I hope you understand.
I don't think it's the worst thing
in the world to fight,
because we can talk it out
like this afterward.
But Mimi doesn't know what's going on,
and she might be worried.
She might be blaming herself for this
'cause she went on the date.
- That's the kind of girl she is.
- Mmm.
You probably know that.
- That's what bothered me.
- Right.
The other thing with this is,
if you, me, and Maru
keep fighting over her like that,
then the other girls
are gonna start thinking,
"Oh, so all three of them are into Mimi,"
and they might bully her all over again.
- Mmm.
- That's what I didn't want.
- I want to stop that from happening.
And to be honest with you,
when someone tells me to get my ass
outside in front of everyone like that,
- it flips my switch.
- Mmm.
I should've kept myself under control.
End of the day, we're fine.
But I think she's feeling it
the worst right now.
For her sake, I hope you know that.
Mmm, I get it now.
I'll apologize to Mimi too.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
- Ready?
- Let's go back.
Oof, let's do it.
- Yeah, what I did was wrong.
- It takes two to tango, man.
- Took the wrong approach.
- You guys good?
- Yeah. Sorry for making a scene.
- You all right?
Sorry, guys.
It's ringing.
Please excuse the short notice,
but we have arranged sauna time
for the men.
- For real?
- What?
- Whoa.
- Fucking awesome!
- Seriously? Hell yeah!
- So dope. Yeah.
Crazy. Might as well jump in the ocean.
This is dope. Let's go.
- Look at them high-fiving already.
- Anything water-related, they're in.
- "Anything water-related."
- So true!
SAUNA
Whoa, wait, wait, wait.
This place looks kind of familiar.
Kazuma, go jump in first.
- Isn't it too soon?
- Can we just go in?
- Okay, let's do it.
- Open the door!
- All right.
- It's boiling!
- Watch your head.
- So hot!
- I'm on fire!
- This is extra intense.
- Sit down.
- This is the best!
I have a question. How was it with her?
Good question.
- Go on.
- We shared a bed.
- Nice.
- What about… Did you…
- No, we didn't.
- You didn't?
- You really didn't?
- No, we didn't.
- You were a gentleman?
- That's right.
- Yeah?
- She fall asleep in your arms?
- That's all.
- Respect.
Get out of here with that cool guy act.
He's trying hard to play it cool.
I was the only one who bet you'd kiss her.
Really?
He's not in a position to say that!
Seriously, why tempt fate like that,
you know?
Rune and I talked about this,
actually, remember?
Oh, yeah, we did.
He was like, "If she wants it,
I'm ready to make a move."
- I had 1,000 opportunities last night.
- Oh, for real?
Like, while we were drinking,
she'd shift her body a little,
and suddenly, she's this close to my face.
Right.
- But I was like, "Not the right time."
- Know what?
I can see you ordering nonstop champagne
at a hostess bar.
You're an easy target.
- I'll keep myself under control there.
- That's impressive.
At Mimi's club, you'd be ordering
and popping bottles nonstop.
I would've kissed her if it were me.
- You would?
- Me too.
Kazuma would lose his nerve.
- Think I'd chicken out?
- No way I'm telling you.
- This thing goes by so fast.
- It's over before you know it.
- Seriously, so fast.
- Tai-chan, you're not done yet, right?
- You're gonna flunk again.
- Again?
- Nah, I've had enough.
- You'll be on round three.
- Don't worry, I'll stay with you.
- No way.
Wait, are you going bald?
- Am I?
- Must be the stress.
Am I really?
But honestly, I'm glad I stayed here.
Glad I got the chance, you know?
For me, it's not even
just about finding love anymore.
- I feel like I've grown as a person.
- I feel the same way.
- Yeah, you know?
- Seriously.
- Ready to go?
- To the ocean? Let's do it.
- Hell yeah!
- Go.
Argh, I'm cooked.
- Let's take a dip.
- It's hot!
- So hot!
- Ryopi, your sandals!
Here we go!
- Yeah!
- No!
Oh, man. Whoa, it's so shallow.
- Whoa!
- This feels so damn good.
- A cold bath. I bet that's nice.
- This looks like so much fun.
Whoa!
- Hell yeah!
- This is awesome!
- Holy cow, that's good!
- So nice.
- This is the best!
- Man, this is amazing.
- God!
- Unreal!
- Beautiful, right?
- This is so dope.
- Sun's shining.
- Incredible.
Let's huddle up.
- Let's go, you bastards!
- Let's go!
Never give up!
Together, we can all win!
You hear me?
We busted our asses to get here!
Here we go, boys!
What are we even doing?
That's such a beautiful shot.
- Hurray for the damn water.
- Yep, hurray.
"Hurray for the damn water."
Hurray to the water indeed.
It's the final stretch now.
We gotta give it our all.
Mmm-hmm.
Just all went by in a flash.
I blinked, it's almost over.
Me and Ryopi haven't been on one date yet.
- True.
- I really want to.
What even is a date, you know?
What does romance really mean?
That's deep.
Not really. It was shallow.
Another beautiful shot.
- They were fighting five minutes ago.
- Unbelievable.
Then jumped into the ocean.
Then suddenly, all these tough guys
are laying in the sun.
- I know.
- Using each other as pillows.
- Aw. That's youth.
- "What does romance even mean?"
Can we send them home now or what?
I mean, I think they bonded.
Speaking of bonding,
I've been thinking about Rune
and how, in his interview about Mimi,
he was saying over and over
how he had so much fun that night.
But the fact he snapped that hard
makes me think
maybe he was actually frustrated that
he couldn't get as close to Mimi
as he was hoping.
- Yeah.
- And wanted to blame someone for that.
Like, "You guys butted in right when
we wanted to focus on each other."
- You have your gym shoes?
- Shoot, I left mine.
Here, can I have the ball?
RINRIN (20)
HOSTESS
Of course. They're the same age.
- The exact same age.
- That's right.
KAHOCHI (20)
HOSTESS
Shooting from this side,
hit the upper-left corner of that square.
Whoa. You're like a coach.
Look, it's so pretty.
Totally.
I actually don't think
I'm into anyone here yet, to be honest.
- Maybe it'll take time.
- Other than Kazuma, I guess.
I mean, who knows, he might be into Sara,
but I can't just do nothing.
Right.
Once things settle down,
everyone should come back to Okinawa,
and we can all hang out.
- I'd love that.
- Right? Great.
- It's nice we're the same age.
- Totally.
We were looking out at the ocean, smoking…
and just chatting.
It's so great to have someone my age.
I mean, it just makes that person
easier to talk to.
For some reason,
all my friends are Capricorns.
Isn't that weird? Kaho's a Capricorn too.
Rinrin must be into astrology.
- Don't you agree?
- Yeah, strong opinions on that.
By the way, what's your sign, Nagano?
Oh, I'm actually a Virgo.
- Oh.
- I see.
I knew you were gonna react that way.
I didn't wanna tell you.
We really click.
I don't have to hold back at all.
I can be myself with her.
Even back in my hometown,
I'm one of those people
that only needs a few friends I can trust.
With Kahochi,
I feel like I can really see us
being friends later.
She's not just another person
in the group.
I want her around as a friend.
Yeah, at the end of the day,
I guess Kahochi means a lot to me now.
- Oh, that's good for them.
- Really on the same wavelength.
Definitely.
Hmm, I don't like
super skinny guys, but that tummy--
- He has a good build.
- That tummy, though.
You guys mind if I fart?
- You nuts? Jesus, go outside.
- Go for it.
Ew!
On that note, I'm gonna go smoke.
Gotta be kidding.
- Stinking up the room.
- Flap your blanket. I bet it's gonna--
Wait, stop!
Ugh, I can practically smell it.
Through the screen?
It's that powerful.
I swear I just smelled it.
Kahochi's cracking up.
Hey, stop spreading it all over the room!
- I'm going out for a smoke.
- Gosh.
- Yeah, I could use a smoke break too.
- It stinks!
- Evacuate.
- Hey!
It reeks!
- Hey.
- Mmm-mmm.
- Oh, it's these two.
- The devoted Kazuma.
So you guys went into the sauna together?
- All of us.
- Just the guys?
Yep.
- Did Rune and Tai-chan make up?
- Yeah, those two made up.
And Maru apologized too.
Maru was so pissed, wasn't he?
Maru was furious, I know.
I was so surprised.
- Yeah, me too.
- We all were.
I guess that's what he's like
when he loses it.
- He was going full beast mode, for real.
- Yeah.
That was nuts.
So, are my feelings
getting through to you?
I mean, obviously. You know?
I mean, aren't we the only people
doing one-on-ones
with the same person every day?
Probably. How do you really feel, though?
You wanna talk to the other guys?
Well, yeah, of course I do.
Because, like,
we're living together, you know?
- Mmm-hmm.
- I do think about it.
- You do?
- 'Cause opportunities are running out.
Mmm-hmm, mmm.
Hmm.
So, I don't know what to do with Kazuma.
I can't bring myself
to ask him to come smoke with me.
No, you should ask him.
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
I tend to be pretty forward.
- Really?
- With Maru.
I ask him.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
So, yeah, I think
you should definitely ask him.
Yeah, you're right.
By the way, Maru has someone else
he's pretty interested in too.
- Oh, yeah?
- He's got options.
But, for me, I feel like Maru is special.
I think I really like him.
That's why I make sure to tell him
straight up. Like, "Let's go hang out."
Hmm. I guess
I'm just a little shy about it.
- Is that what it is?
- Yeah.
I get that.
I've never done that with guys before.
Hey, we're just having a quick smoke.
And I was telling her I feel like
I can't make bold moves on my own.
- Not much time left.
- True.
- Yeah.
- No, I know.
I think you'll regret it
if you don't go for it.
- Mmm.
- I think so too.
No doubt about it.
Whenever I have
the one-on-one with Kazuma,
he always brings up Sara.
I've never been in a situation before
where a guy wouldn't look my way.
Never. I'm like, "Are you kidding me?"
Come on!
Kazuma,
someone's carrying a torch for you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I get into street fights.
Ah, excuse me, guys.
- Hey.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- What do you want?
- I'm Ryopi, and I'm here for my interview.
Thank you for having me, ma'am.
- Have a seat and wait your turn.
- Come on, man, don't butt in.
- Put a sock in it.
- Ryopi's making his move.
Don't get too flirty, okay?
Man, she's cracking up.
- That's a hard no.
- She laughs that hard?
I'd like to request a change.
Change of hostess!
- Why's that?
- She's a nice girl.
She laughs like a mad scientist
who's gonna destroy the world.
Man, you're funny.
Nailed it.
- The three of us are like siblings now.
- Right?
Yeah. Why do I feel this comfortable?
It's funny, we've barely talked until now,
so this feels kind of new, huh?
It does. Are you getting butterflies?
Huh? I thought that was you.
- Whoa.
- Like, is it time?
- What do you mean?
- Time for me to move to Okinawa. Duh.
Should I open a bar in Okinawa?
- Could you, please? Do it.
- Yeah, sure.
Cool. Do you come to Okinawa a lot?
- I do.
- Oh, yeah?
I went to Ta-taki Waterfall.
Oh, yeah, the water there feels amazing.
- It felt so damn good.
- That place is awesome.
At the end, I jumped in
from somewhere super-high.
- Like, boing.
- You dived?
- Were you okay?
- My nuts hurt bad.
- That's rough. That's really gotta hurt.
- I was like, "Oh, my God!"
Felt like a baseball bat to the crotch.
I bet we're the only ones
talking about crude stuff.
Mmm-hmm. Thumbs up from me.
- Okay, so, what's your type?
- No.
Don't gimme that.
That's not how a conversation works.
I asked a Q, so give me an A.
That's what Q&A means!
Let's get a little back and forth going.
- Okay, what's your type?
- I don't know.
- We're done here.
- Dead-end conversation.
- Seriously, you're the hardest to read.
- I get that a lot.
Actually, I get that a lot too.
We're just a couple
of unreadable people. Yay!
Well, I mean, I know Kazuma has feelings
for me, so, yeah, you know…
Trust me, you won't find someone
who's that into you.
I know. That's definitely true, but…
Let me guess, you don't like it
when things get too clingy.
- Exactly.
- Right? Same here, most of the time.
- It's all about space, right?
- Exactly. Space is important.
- It's about breathing room.
- True that.
So maybe seeing each other
only on weekends would work.
- Yeah, maybe.
- That'd be easy, right?
That way, we don't have to stick our noses
into each other's business.
For sure. That'd be good.
- We're kinda similar, huh?
- Yeah.
So what now?
Yikes, bail, bail, bail, bail.
What? Don't bail on me!
Me and Ryopi were just cracking up
the whole time, talking about crude stuff.
Just when we start having
a real conversation,
one of us starts joking around.
He's just so easy to talk to. Seriously.
He might actually be interesting.
So that was my first
one-on-one conversation with Sara.
And, yeah,
it was really comfortable talking to her.
We just really clicked.
You never know until you give it a shot.
Now that we've talked, I'm starting
to see her in a different light.
- Oh, that's good.
- Wait, was that their first one-on-one?
I think so.
- First real chat?
- Yes, their first.
They look good together.
- Right.
- Don't they?
Watching this show makes me realize
people change so much
depending on who they're with.
- Mmm.
- That's true.
Different sides of their personalities
emerge, they can be so different.
We were seeing
a version of her we've never seen.
- Yes.
- And with Ryopi.
But then again,
she knows Kazuma's still there.
She knows he's had a thing for her
since day one.
The guy is so devoted.
But, you know,
I still can't help but feel like
she was more herself with Ryopi.
- That's true.
- Wow, the action finally begins.
- Love it.
- Mmm.
- Just in time for the show to wrap up.
- How many episodes are left?
We're deep into the second half already.
We have two episodes left.
- Two episodes?
- So they have to go bam, bam, bam.
- How much can this develop?
- That's what I'm saying.
- Can we talk?
- Uh, sure, okay.
- I wanted to apologize first.
- Okay.
I really screwed up.
No, don't worry about it at all.
There's a lot going on, so it's okay.
- Like, when you were leaving the school…
- Yeah.
When I thought I might not get to see you
anymore, I felt like all I could do was…
what I did back there.
You wrote that in your letter too,
about what happened during Part 1.
I put myself out there like that
because I wanted to make my feelings
clear to you even just a little.
Whether that was the right move or not…
Right.
…that's for you to decide.
Mmm-hmm.
I just felt I owed you an apology
before anything else.
- So I'm sorry.
- Mmm, it's totally fine. I'm okay with it.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- You have fun on the date?
- Well…
- You mean with Rune?
- Uh-huh.
The setting was something
totally different, so yeah.
It was fun in a way, but, hmm…
To be honest, I'm interested in you,
but I'm interested in Rune too.
Mmm.
I went on that date,
but I wasn't sure how I felt.
- Sure.
- So I was just nervous the whole time.
I felt like
I finally started to relax at the end.
Well, I still really like you.
Yeah, I know that.
And we don't have much time to talk.
- That's a problem.
- There's a lot going on.
But the reality is…
- "Reality" is a scary word.
- Yeah. But for real, um…
I'm gonna keep taking
everything I learned in Part 1
and try my best to apply it here.
Uh-huh.
I'm just gonna keep putting
my honest feelings out there.
- So, yeah.
- All right, I gotcha.
Even when he says all that,
she's like, "Okay."
- She's so reserved.
- Maybe she's just shy.
That's what I thought.
Maybe she's always had trouble
expressing her true feelings.
LOVE DINER
- Hey there.
- Whoa.
- I've been waiting for you.
- What's up?
Wow, it's kinda… kinda crazy.
- Mimi sure is popular.
- She is.
She's kinda the prom queen, right?
Of course she is.
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
I guess everyone loves that kinda of face.
- Right?
- It's not just about her looks.
It's what's inside too.
So…
does that mean
Mimi is the only one for you now?
The one on your mind?
Mmm…
Yeah, my feelings for her
still haven't changed. Not at all.
All right, then.
Mmm.
- So, what exactly do you like about Mimi?
- You really asking?
Well, Mimi is, uh…
really straightforward,
you know, as a person.
She's the kind of woman who makes you
notice things you wouldn't otherwise.
- Mmm-hmm.
- She's so present, you know?
When I'm around her, she makes me alive
to the world in a different way.
I feel like she makes me
see things clearly somehow.
Mmm.
So it's not about her having
a pretty face or anything like that.
- It's about who she is.
- Mmm-hmm, yeah.
That's what usually
draws me closer to someone.
Yeah, like,
someone grounded on the inside.
- Mmm…
- Yeah.
That's what you like.
Well, obviously, I can tell
that's where your heart is now.
So, yeah…
I'll give you up then.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Completely.
All right?
I mean, I'm totally out now.
- Hmm?
- So thanks.
- Are you--
- I'm done, so…
Mmm-hmm. It's no big deal anymore.
- Thanks, though.
- Good night.
Bye-bye.
She kept saying, "I'm done, I'm out."
- That was a little…
- Yeah, she still has feelings.
- Tai-chan has no feelings for her at all.
- Yeah.
I think she came over to confirm that,
which was a brave move.
And Tai-chan, I don't think
he could've done that in Part 1.
- No, no way.
- He's changed.
He probably said all that so he could
help Sharan find what she's looking for.
- Mmm.
- Good point.
- Takes guts.
- I mean, what he likes about Mimi.
- Kazuma, how's it going? Making progress?
- This guy's a wizard.
- Mmm-hmm, I've gotten pretty far.
- That's looking good.
That's impressive.
If you have time, can you draw one for me?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm on a tight schedule here, buddy.
I got no time.
- For real?
- That's awesome!
- He's drawing this for Sara, remember?
- That's the one he's giving to her.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Giving me the cold shoulder?
- Oh, wow.
- You're good.
- You've made a lot of progress.
- That's dope.
He's in the zone.
- Hold on.
- What?
- What now?
- Come on!
- What is it?
- What the hell?
- Everyone's like, "What now?"
- Good morning, everyone.
Morning.
Only four days until the confession.
We know.
The men will ask out
the women they're interested in.
Get to know them better.
Here comes Kazuma.
Using the PA system,
the men will announce their choice.
Choose wisely.
This may be your last chance.
In the event that a woman
is chosen by more than one man,
she should meet with the one who she wants
to build
a deeper emotional connection with.
I don't like this!
- Why are you looking at me?
- Good luck choosing.
- No, no, no, no.
- Oh, it's this one.
Yeah, here it is.
Calling girls out with the school's
PA system? This is nerve-wracking.
- This is good.
- Yeah, this is a good one.
All right.
Kamaken's choice is gonna be
obvious. They've been pretty steady.
I hope you're right.
- Check, check.
- Kazuma?
Yo, mic check, one-two.
- Not Kazuma.
- Is it Ryopi?
It's Kamaken.
Oh, really?
- Oh! She wants the invite.
- Nice. Yeah.
So, today,
the person I want to talk to is…
This is scary.
…Rinrin.
I'll be in our room.
- Oh, it's the guys' room.
- Come on over.
All right, peace.
- All right, peace!
- Peace out!
Aw, the look on her face!
- Rinrin's adorable.
- She's so cute.
- Her dimples are adorable.
- That smile.
- I'm so happy!
- This is freaky!
This is nerve-wracking.
I'm kinda mortified.
ON AIR
Check, check. Hey.
Uh, this is Kazuma.
So, the girl I want to talk to today is…
Who could it be?
…Sara.
I'll be waiting for you
at the smoking area on the second floor.
- Smoking area, interesting.
- He's so funny.
That will be all.
Just like a teacher.
He's always so funny. Oh, my gosh.
How does he always manage
to lighten the mood?
Everyone's blood pressure goes down
when he's around.
- Yeah, mic check, one-two.
- Oh, it's Rune.
Rune here.
Uh, the girl I want to invite
to a one-on-one is…
Such a rapper.
…Mimi.
Come to the smoking spot behind the gym.
- That's a good choice.
- So romantic. Ooh, la, la.
- Good spot.
- He's a sly one.
Test, test.
This is Maru.
And the girl I would like
to talk to alone today is…
The suspense.
- Leaving us hanging.
- Yeah.
…is Mimi.
I'll be waiting at the smoking area
in the courtyard.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'd be like that too.
- Whoa, Ayacheru!
- Ayacheru.
So he picks Mimi.
Hmm, you've already got
two guys to choose from.
- You gotta pick.
- No, but--
Yeah.
All right, let's do this, man.
Good morning, boys and girls!
This is Ryopi!
Wait, is he playing a YouTube video?
And the girl I'd like to invite
for a little one-on-one time is…
Wow, he's good, huh?
Dum!
…Sara!
- Whoa.
- What? Really?
He's gotta be kidding me. Come on, man,
that's a sneaky move right there!
I'll be waiting in the living room
on the second floor, so come on up!
- No way.
- What?
- "Come on up," cute.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Wow.
- What does this mean?
- I'm surprised.
- Wait. That was so unexpected, right?
- I know.
Let's do this.
She's all mine.
I'm on a roll, and I'm unstoppable.
Mmm, it's pretty hard
to sit here and wait for it.
Right? Like…
- They're switching.
- Yeah.
Yo, yo.
Um, Tai-chan in the house.
And the girl that I really want
to talk to today is…
Mimi.
Let's continue our conversation
from yesterday because it ain't over yet.
Meet me on the beach
in front of the sauna.
I'll be waiting.
- That spot is so nice.
- Perfect place.
- Whoa.
- Choices, choices.
Man, oh, man.
- Poor Sharan.
- Gosh. You okay, Sharan?
I really am gonna have
a hard time choosing.
Like, "I should talk to dot, dot, dot."
It's tough.
- Dot, dot, dot, who knows?
- It's a close one.
- Have fun.
- I'm gonna head out.
Be careful.
- Live it up.
- Have a good time.
- See you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Who is she going to meet?
Please, please. Come to me.
Yes, she came!
- Hey, Tai-chan.
- I've been waiting for you.
Dang, I'm so happy. I was praying.
I'm so happy for him!
Tai-chan!
Go, Tai-chan!
Can we end the show here?
- We can't.
- Come on!
We still have a full four days left.
Wait, really?
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Here we go.
- Man, I'm glad I said a little prayer.
So you prayed, huh?
- Want a blanket?
- Oh. No.
- Okay.
- I'm fine.
Was it a tough choice?
Well, I mean, in terms of my feelings…
Hmm?
…if I'm being honest, I guess a part of me
is still kind of unsure even now.
- But I wanted to talk to you first.
- Okay. So I have to make you choose me.
I got this. I won't lose, no matter what.
Hearing what you said yesterday,
I could sense you weren't sure about Rune.
You're right.
- Oh, yeah?
- You're not wrong.
But now you're having kind of a…
a hard time making a decision, right?
- Yeah, it's hard.
- Right.
I mean, I don't know how to put it,
but… Hmm, like, well…
Yeah?
Well, I know how Sharan feels about you.
- Mmm.
- So there's definitely that too.
Mmm.
And, you know,
I think it's amazing how Rune
is so straightforward and everything,
so it's all really complicated.
Uh-huh, mmm.
Right, right.
But I don't have any doubts at all.
- Mmm.
- For real, none.
- Yeah?
- Mmm.
There's only one option for me.
And honestly,
it makes me feel
really glad I stayed here.
I mean that.
I'm just gonna keep trying
and make you fall for me.
- Leave it to me.
- I look forward to it.
- Mmm.
- I can't wait.
- It is what is.
- Nothing we can do about it.
- We still have four days.
- Yeah, we still have a shot.
All he's getting right now
is one little moment.
- Right.
- We'll get another chance.
- But Tai-chan, really?
- Right?
- To think they were fighting.
- So true.
- Can we see them?
- See 'em?
- I think we can see them from here.
- Are they by the sauna?
- I can't quite get a view.
- I guess not.
Seeing them made me mad,
so I shouldn't look.
- I hope it starts pouring.
- Lightning strikes.
- This is cute.
- I know.
Can I write something? Real quick.
Do it.
What does "Taisei" mean?
- "Big, bright star."
- There we go.
- Mmm.
- "Star." That's so cool.
- I know.
Hmm…
This is just like a movie.
- Okay, I'm done.
- Can I see it?
- Huh?
- Let me see it.
Yeah, come.
Can you read it out loud?
I LIKE MIMI SO MUCH
- No way!
- Why not? Are you embarrassed?
Yeah, a little.
Well, this is how I feel.
So? Are my feelings coming across?
- I'd say so.
- That's good.
Sorry, I'm always too straightforward.
- No, stop. I'm happy. I really am.
- Mmm.
Mmm.
I feel super blessed.
And I wanna say
thank you for choosing to meet me.
And my feelings aren't going to change.
I like you so much.
Aw, that was cute!
- Sorry, I can't help myself.
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
- Hmm.
- Come here.
- Huh? For what?
No, I'm paralyzed with anticipation!
- Wait, what?
- I think… I'm stuck like this.
- Thank you.
- Mmm.
Is this love?
My heart was pounding.
It definitely felt like love.
I think Tai-chan is more…
exciting and free
in terms of how he behaves
and expresses himself around me.
He was going to write his feelings
in the sand.
He wrote "I like Mimi so much."
Terrible handwriting.
He was hurt by that.
He's cute.
When I look at his face, my heart pounds.
To be honest, my heart
doesn't pound like that with Rune.
But with him, I feel a sense of security.
She was being a lot looser
than she was with Rune, wasn't she?
- She seemed more natural.
- She seemed softer around him too.
I found myself thinking that
they might end up together.
- Oh!
- Tai-chan is so straightforward.
- Yeah.
- Maybe that's kind of refreshing?
- Exactly.
She works at a hostess club,
so she must've learned
a lot of mind tricks.
- Ah. That's true.
- So considering that,
wouldn't she think
Tai-chan's attitude is cute?
"I like Mimi so much."
- He wrote in the sand!
- Really cute!
- Okay, I'm going.
- Enjoy.
- I'm excited.
- Make the most of it.
- Have fun. Show off those dimples, Rinrin.
- Shut up.
It's so cold. What are you doing?
- Have you been a naughty girl?
- You're dumb.
- What did you think?
- Think about what?
When you heard me say, "It's Kamaken."
- Oh, that's what you're asking?
- Did you think I'd choose you?
No, actually, we had no idea
who you would choose.
But I chose you, Rinrin.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Sure did.
So, are you worried about anything?
- Nope, nothing.
- Nothing at all?
What about you? Are you worried?
Have you ever cheated?
- Nope.
- Are you sure?
No, I haven't!
Oh, that's what you're worried about?
Yeah, a little.
The thing is, when I get a boyfriend,
I stop going out, like, completely.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm either home or with the girls.
If I go out at all,
it's always with my female friends.
- I've never cheated, and I couldn't.
- Right, mmm.
I usually don't get super interested
in guys like this.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm glad that
you told me how you feel despite that.
It means a lot.
Yeah, I just don't feel this way
very often.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm special?
Yeah, I guess.
Ryopi and I had some stuff
going on at first, though.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- Did you guys kiss? There was a rumor.
- Right, he kissed me. Mmm…
- What?
- Mmm… Mmm…
Yeah, he may or may not have kissed me.
- I don't know, man.
- But that was well before I showed up.
- Yeah, it was.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, I've been meaning
to tell you about that, but…
I don't mind at all, no big deal.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- For sure.
- I was like, "Oh, that happened."
- Right.
Like this? Lips to lips?
Mmm, I guess.
- It also happened right here.
- No way.
That's so funny.
So should I kiss you on the cheek?
I don't know, I'm kinda shy.
If you want me to, I'll do it.
On the cheek, though.
Then do it.
No, no, I'm so embarrassed.
Nice, nice, nice.
You can tell they're comfortable.
The man's gotta take the first step.
I wasn't gonna do it
if you said you were too embarrassed,
but you gave the green light.
- So I had to follow through.
- Oof, my brain's not working right now.
What should I do?
I feel like, "Ooh, ooh, ooh."
You sleepy?
LADIES
- Oh, man.
- Have fun.
- Enjoy yourself.
- Good luck.
I wonder where she's headed.
My sweet big sis, Sara.
- Bye, babes.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Sara.
- See you later.
Well, guys,
Little Kaho is going to turn in.
I'm going to dream about
getting picked by all the guys here.
- Tough to not be chosen at all.
- Poor girls.
Yeah, especially after
being here for this long.
No!
Come on, don't do that to him!
Oh. I knew it.
Yes!
Oh, my God!
- Is it awkward to sit right next to you?
- No, it's fine. I don't mind.
- After you.
- With your permission.
I was trying to entertain myself.
I gotta say, I was so surprised.
- Thought you'd be.
- The girls' room was buzzing.
- Oh, really?
- Seriously.
- I was buzzing doing the announcement.
- I bet. Everyone was shocked.
- Like, "Oh, what?"
- Yeah.
- I can imagine.
- Mmm.
The reason I decided to come to you
is 'cause I wanted to tell you…
I mean, I know we've only talked
a little bit up to this point, right?
Twice.
But I realized
what a good listener you are.
- You pick up on the way I'm feeling.
- Aw, thanks.
And I've never really
experienced that before.
- I just--
- Yeah, we have a lot in common too.
- Mmm, I know, right?
- Yeah.
- Turns out we're similar.
- For sure, we think the same way.
We value our space
and don't want things to get too clingy.
- Yeah, exactly.
- I think you understand me.
And in the end,
it made me decide to come to you.
- Gotcha.
- Right.
Yeah. After yesterday,
I definitely think we're compatible.
Yeah. I just like talking to you the most.
- Well, yeah, only--
- What?
I mean, I agree.
But there are a few people
I feel comfortable with here.
- I like talking to Rinrin too.
- Sure.
Yeah, Rinrin's fun to be around,
but I feel like I'm doing all the talking.
But that sense of ease…
- With me?
- Yeah.
- Your sense of calmness and ease.
That's what really struck me.
Man, you're so funny.
No, but the other thing is,
I do feel kinda bad for Kazuma
because, um,
he's, like, making you a drawing.
- Yeah, that's been a big thing, right?
- Right. Oh, yeah.
That's why I thought
I wouldn't get picked.
- Oh, did you?
- Mmm.
- Yeah, we all see him drawing for you.
- Right, yeah.
- Wow, am I doing something shitty?
- Well, if you are, so am I.
- Yeah, we're both responsible, no doubt.
- We both have blood on our hands.
Yeah, from here on out,
it's a head-to-head battle with Kazuma.
Poor Kazuma!
But they're accomplices now.
- Psychologically speaking.
- Yeah, true.
- That might heat up.
- Being partners in crime is the best fuel
for their romantic fire, right?
I hope Kazuma gets wise to that soon
and goes to Kahochi.
- I know, Kahochi still has a chance.
- I think she does.
- Yeah.
- She's started a little behind…
- But we don't know what might happen.
- Yeah.
- What you doing?
- Where's he?
- I don't know.
- This is insane, right?
She's with Tai-chan now, but, you know,
first, she walked past Maru
then right past me.
- You saw her too?
- It sucked.
That's tough.
Yikes.
- That hurts. I bet you're pissed, huh?
- Yeah.
- That messes with your head.
- Sorry, guys.
- I don't like it.
- Should we do something?
- I wouldn't do that.
- You wouldn't, right?
- Definitely not.
- Let's make something.
- We can do that.
- What should we make?
Hmm…
Would you mind
if I go sort out my thoughts a little?
- Sure, of course.
- Okay.
- I gotcha.
- I get it.
- Take your time.
- Thanks.
- Mmm.
- Good idea.
- Sorry about that.
- It's okay. It's all good.
We're all feeling like crap anyway.
HEAD OVER HEELS
- What's she doing?
- Where's she going?
- She's taking her purse.
- Yeah.
Huh?
She's going to the gate.
And then?
- Wait… What?
- Uh…
So I guess she picked Tai-chan.
- Are you shocked and sad?
- Yeah.
I kind of expected her
to go with Tai-chan,
but to be honest, your announcement
was pretty unexpected as well.
How so?
I mean, all the girls were like, "Really?"
- About the person I chose?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Uh-huh.
- But I gotta say, I saw it coming.
- Oh, you did? Interesting.
- Yeah, so it wasn't a huge thing.
I didn't…
feel too hurt.
I wasn't down in the dumps.
SHARAN, RINRIN, KAHOCHI
Finishing touches. We gotta wait
for the right moment to show these.
- Surprise. That what you meant?
- Yeah.
That's so nice.
Oh, my God, they'll definitely
be happy to see these.
Oh, it's looking good. Wow, isn't it cute?
Oh, that's incredible. You're a genius.
Check it out. It's all about getting
that handcrafted touch, you know?
- Beautiful. Aren't these amazing?
- They're nice.
Wait, these look better than I expected.
They're awesome, huh?
It's all about nailing the presentation.
So pretty!
- I'm speechless!
- Is this a bakery?
Even a cake shop
couldn't make something like this.
Maru and his baking skills…
No kidding.
- His talent is just…
- Blossoming.
- It's blossoming, right?
- 100%!
It wasn't romance or a girl.
- It was baking!
- Yes!
- That's what he found here.
- He found a passion for cakes.
- He's a pastry chef.
- Pastry chef! Both are!
Hang on. This is a reality dating show,
not a job fair.
"The social reintegration project:
Find your career here."
That's more like it.
- Where did Sharan go, anyway?
- Sharan?
Yeah.
She might want
to be alone with her thoughts
'cause of Tai-chan's announcement.
All right, everyone.
Let's continue preparations
for the locals' thank-you party.
I'm gonna paint here too.
- Yeah.
- Leave some for us, though.
Why don't you leave
this part on the left side?
- Okay.
- Okay. For Kamaken?
No, Mimi said
she wanted to paint a little.
- Really? It's kinda--
- Yeah.
- Wow, the paint's out!
- We're painting.
We're trying to get the first coat on.
I was gonna go change real quick.
- Nice. Go ahead and change.
- All good?
- I wanna try.
- Looking good.
- No idea what I'm doing.
- Nice. Suits you.
- Same. Just pretend.
- How do you do it?
- Come here.
- Like Picasso.
Don't spread it too thin.
- Paint the parts you like for now.
- Too much?
- Really?
- Just like that.
Good work. Nice.
- Don't get in the way. Stop it!
- Don't mess around!
- Can I borrow Kazuma for a second?
- Sure.
Kazuma, let's talk.
- Let's go for a smoke.
- Oh, sure.
He wants to do the right thing.
Yeah, so there's something
I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
Well, look, obviously,
you know that Sara came to see me.
And I know about your feelings for her,
so, you know, I don't want
to get in the way of that.
Well, I don't need pity or compassion
when it comes to her--
It's not about me pitying you.
This isn't me
trying to stir up trouble or anything.
I just wanted
to get in front of it and be honest.
Gotcha. Thanks for clearing that up.
I don't have any reason to be angry.
Well, then, I guess
it's Badly In Love from here on out.
- So you're going for her now?
- Uh-huh.
Well, she might've picked you today,
but I plan to keep pushing
until the last minute.
- Yeah.
- Just so you know.
Looks like I picked the most formidable
guy here as a rival, huh?
Yeah, I don't plan on losing.
- Let's do this.
- I'll need that competitive edge to win.
I just wanted to talk it out.
All right then, may the best man win.
I'm gonna charge ahead until the last day.
'Course you are.
I turned out to be a dark horse.
- I was surprised to see you here.
- Nice work!
Yay! It turned out okay!
- So cool!
- Watch out.
- Yikes!
- My gosh, close call.
- Super close.
- That's a relief.
- Give her some room.
- Wasn't like they'd fall apart.
Maru's taking another shot
at these burgers.
Crazy, right?
If anyone asks, it's my signature dish.
"What are you making, Chef?"
"Hamburger steaks."
Gotta say it with a little attitude.
You've gotten a lot better
since the first day.
- It's crazy.
- Seriously.
He's more confident too.
Dude is in the zone. Those look good.
- Right?
- Second time's the charm, I guess.
Nice, nice.
- Is Maru a genius?
- Yeah, a culinary genius.
I keep thinking
Ryopi and Maru should open a restaurant.
- Interesting idea.
- Ryopi can run it.
- He's the owner.
- The manager.
And Maru can give
his full attention to baking.
Ah.
- All cakes all the time.
- Maru would go, "Ryopi, I pick you."
- No, no.
- "Let's be partners in crime!"
- "We found each other!"
- You've corrupted Awich.
- They leave as a couple, right? So sweet.
- No, guys. Remember, dating show.
- Where'd Sharan go?
- Add water and you're done.
- I have no idea.
- You're right. She's gone.
- We haven't seen Sharan.
- Sharan's not here.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
She wasn't around when we came in, right?
Um, yeah but she was with us
before we started working on the bench.
I think she said
she wanted to be alone for a bit.
- Okay.
- She said that and left.
- Should we be worried?
- What was wrong?
I thought about offering to go, but…
- Give her space.
- She want to be alone?
She said she wanted to be by herself,
so I didn't wanna follow her.
If she wanted to go home
or something, I'd try to talk to her,
but if she just needs a minute to think,
then maybe we should give her that space.
I respect it.
- Do it one by one.
- Hold on.
- I feel I should go.
- Big one's for the guys.
- Can I sit next to you?
- Yeah, go right ahead.
- These are for the girls.
- Give me.
Everyone seems on edge.
I feel like I should go look for Sharan.
- Napkins, anyone?
- I want to go too.
- I can go. I don't mind.
- Hmm…
Well, then I'll leave it to you, I guess.
- We can't all go.
- Kazuma, let's go for now.
- Let's go.
- We're counting on you.
- Eat. Go ahead and start.
- Yeah, eat.
- This might take a while.
- Yeah.
Well, we'll wait for you for a minute.
We don't know where she is, though.
- You can eat. It's fine.
- Dig in while it's hot.
- Hello? Sharan?
- Are you here?
No sign of her.
- She isn't here?
- Huh.
Sharan?
- She's not here.
- She sleeping or something?
- She's not here?
- Nope.
Where is she?
Wait, was her purse there?
Sharan.
- Don't see her.
- No way.
- Huh? Where is she?
- Really?
There's a cake.
She's the one we're celebrating.
- Oh, you're right.
- Yeah.
Yeah, we're celebrating her today.
Did you find her? Any sign of her?
- Let's try the PA room.
- This is not like her.
- Go back to dinner.
- Can I go in first?
I'm going in first.
- You sure?
- I think a girl should go in first.
Sharan. Huh?
She's not here.
No way.
Not here either.
- Did we look over here?
- Where the hell is she?
- What the…
- What the hell?
You never know, I mean…
- We looked everywhere, couldn't find her.
- Are you serious?
We went all the way
to the back of the sauna, nothing.
- She vanished.
- She's not in our room?
- Nope, she wasn't there.
- She's not anywhere.
She wasn't in her bed.
- The gym?
- Really?
- No sign of her.
- She might have left the school.
- Dropped out?
- Went home?
- For real?
She talked to Tai-chan yesterday.
- Mmm.
- How was she then?
- Yeah.
- Hmm…
- Should I say it? Is it hard to say?
No, I can say it. She was like,
"Thanks for everything up until now."
What?
She said something like,
"Thanks for everything up until now."
That's what she said.
But then…
we ended the conversation.
- Right. So you don't know either.
- Yeah.
- She must have dropped out, right?
- For real?
- You're kidding.
- All of a sudden?
Sounds like
she's done telling Tai-chan how she feels.
Maybe she hinted at it to Tai-chan,
but how could she just leave
without telling any of us?
I don't know.
What the heck?
I mean, there's no rule
that says she has to tell everyone.
Right.
Nothing we can do about it, then.